Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records, [ca.1875]-1981.
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records
- Survey of the Plant of the State Colleges, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Survey of the Heat, Light, Power and Water Utilized, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Report on Action Taken on Proposals, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Report on Colleges of Agriculture, Home Economics and Experiment Station, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Report on Research at Cornell's State Colleges, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Agricultural Economics, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Agronomy, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Animal Husbandry, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Botany, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Conservation, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Dairy Industry, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Entomology and Limnology, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Extension, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Home Economics, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Plant Breeding, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Plant Pathology, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Pomology, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Poultry Husbandry, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Rural Education, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Rural Sociology, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Vegetable Crops, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Professor William B. Ward, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Land Grant College Survey Questionnaire, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Survey of State Colleges of Agriculture, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Reports on Agricultural Colleges, 1928 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Campground Management Conference, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- G.L.F. Proposal, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Opportunities in Agriculture (Box 35, Folder 36)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 37)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 38)
- Agricultural College Council Minutes, 1945-1949 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- College of Agriculture Experiment Station Budget, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1952-1954 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1955-1957 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1958-1961 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1959-1962 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- College of Agriculture Budget, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- College of Agriculture Budget Hearings, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- College of Agriculture Budget Hearings, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Agricultural Chemistry, 1920-1923 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Agricultural Economics and Farm Management, 1921-1924 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Agricultural Economics and Farm Management, 1919-1923 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Agronomy, 1919-1924 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Animal Husbandry, 1921-1924 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Botany, 1920-1924 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Botany Outlines, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Dairy Industry (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Entomology, 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Extension, 1921-1922 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Floriculture, 1919-1924 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Landscape Art, 1920-1922 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Farm Practice, 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Meterology, 1921-1926 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Plant Breeding-Genetics-Prelims, 1921-1922 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Plant Breeding-Genetics-Laboratory Work, 1921-1922 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Plant Breeding-Genetics-Problems, 1921-1922 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Plant Breeding-Advanced Genetics, 1921-1922 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Plant Breeding-Miscellaneous, 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Plant Pathology, 1921-1925 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Pomology, 1920-1930 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Poultry Husbandry, 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Rural Education, 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Rural Engineering, 1920-1924 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Rural Social Organizations, 1921-1923 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Vegetable Gardening, 1921-1924 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Ring Memorial Contest, 1920-1922 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Ring Memorial Contest, 1923-1927 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Ring Memorial Contest, 1928-1937 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Ring Memorial Contest, 1938-1939 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Ring Memorial Contest, 1940-1949 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Ring Memorial Contest, 1950-1955 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Department Questionnaires, 1926 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Agricultural Economics and Farm Management, 1925-1931 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Animal Husbandry, 1928-1930 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Botany, 1925-1931 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Dairy Industry, 1925-1936 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Entomology, 1925-1931 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Extension Training, 1925-1930 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Agronomy, 1925-1931 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Farm Practice, 1920-1931 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Floriculture, 1925-1930 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Forestry, 1925-1930 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Plant Breeding, 1925-1930 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Plant Pathology, 1925-1931 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Poultry Husbandry, 1925-1930 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Rural Education, 1925-1930 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Rural Engineering, 1924-1930 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Rural Social Organization, 1925-1931 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Vegetable Gardening, 1925-1931 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Agricultural Journalism, 1920 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Chemistry, 1923-1929 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Zoology, 1923-1926 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Student Exchange Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Robert Zimmernman - Swedish Exchange, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Mexican Exchange, 1967-1972 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Argentine Exchange, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Argentine Exchange - Pablo Enrique Gomez Riera, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- Cornell Exchange - Scholarship Application (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Douglas K. Bassett, 1974-1975 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Jeff Jacobson - University of Reading - England, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- John R. Meyer, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Professor Paton - Aberdeen, Scotland (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Turk - Retirement Dinner, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Rodd Lewis - Mexican Exchange, 1971-1973 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- Lila Miller - Reading, England, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- Marie Hewes - Philippines, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- Gary Deines - Reading, England, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Paul Screeton Millar - Application, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Kevin Banks - Application, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- Rochelle Woods - Reading, England, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Parra and Viesca - Mexican - Monterrey Exchange, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Eric Ebner - Aberdeen, Scotland, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Timothy Comings - Aberdeen, England, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Charles Huff - Scandinavian Seminar Sweden, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Terence Centner - University of Newcastle on Tyne, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- David Schwartz -University of Edinburgh, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Cynthia Warner - University of Granada, Spain, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- Michael Serinsky - Scandinavian Seminar, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- Student Exchange Program, 1692-1972 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- Special Exchanges, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- Agricultural Exchange, 1962-1970 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Swedish Exchange, 1970-1972 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- Kenneth Davies, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- Stephen Keith Parris, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Student Exchange Information, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Student Exchange Applicants, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Office of Academic Funding, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Admissions, 1961-1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Africana Studies and Research Center, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Arts and Sciences, 1963-1974 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Biochemistry, 1962-1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Buildings and Properties, 1963-1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Bursar's Office, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Business and Public Administration, 1954-1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Calendar, 1967-1982 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Calendar of Public Events, 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Campus Council, 1979 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Laboratory of Cell Physiology, 1963-1969 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Chemistry, 1961-1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Comber - Director of Finance, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Commencement, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Office of Community Relations, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Conference Office, 1972-1979 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Peterson - Controller, 1969-1972 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Alice Cook - Ombudsman, 1970-1971 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Cornell Chronicle, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- COSEP, 1971-1975 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- University Council, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Course Rosters and Examinations, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Dean of Students, 1949-1974 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Byron Saunders - Dean University Faculty, 1974-1976 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Norman Penney - Dean University Faculty, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Robert Miller - Dean University Faculty, 1967-1971 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Emergency Procedures for Students, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- English Department, 1941-1967 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- College of Engineering, 1945-1974 (Box 39, Folder 33)
- Extramural Division, 1962-1974 (Box 39, Folder 34)
- Faculty Council of Representatives, 1971-1976 (Box 39, Folder 35)
- Office of General Services, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 36)
- Geneva Experiment Station, 1962-1974 (Box 39, Folder 37)
- Department of Geology, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 38)
- Grade Distribution, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 39)
- Graduate Faculty, 1956-1960 (Box 39, Folder 40)
- Graduate School, 1950-1975 (Box 39, Folder 41)
- School of Hotel Administration, 1941-1969 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Housing, 1973-1978 (Box 39, Folder 42)
- Resident Halls - Housing and Dining Services, 1955-1975 (Box 39, Folder 43)
- College of Human Ecology, 1962-1974 (Box 39, Folder 44)
- School of Industrial and Labor relations, 1945-1975 (Box 39, Folder 45)
- Institutional Studies, 1966-1971 (Box 39, Folder 46)
- Life Safety Services and Insurance, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 47)
- International Student Office - Foreign Student Counselor, 1946-1973 (Box 39, Folder 48)
- International Studies, 1966-1972 (Box 39, Folder 49)
- Keith Kennedy - Vice-Provost, 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 50)
- Management Systems and Analysis - Samuel Lawrence, Director, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 51)
- Scholarships and Financial Aid - Gary Lee, Director, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 52)
- Graduate School - Paul Leurgans, Dean, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 53)
- University Libraries, 1962-1976 (Box 39, Folder 54)
- Life Safety Services - Toboggan Lodge, 1973-1975 (Box 39, Folder 55)
- Management Systems and Analysis, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 56)
- Medical College - New York City, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 57)
- Medical Services - Gannett Clinic, 1943-1969 (Box 39, Folder 58)
- Dean of Students - Elmer Meyer, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 59)
- Military Science and Tactics, 1954-1966 (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Department of Naval Science, 1951-1964 (Box 39, Folder 61)
- Nutritional Sciences, 1955-1976 (Box 39, Folder 62)
- Ombudsman, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 63)
- Office of Resident Instruction, 1953-1976 (Box 39, Folder 64)
- Personnel Office, 1968-1977 (Box 39, Folder 65)
- Photographic Science, 1948-1967 (Box 39, Folder 66)
- Physical Education Department, 1948-1972 (Box 39, Folder 67)
- Physics Department, 1941-1962 (Box 39, Folder 68)
- University Provost, 1969-1976 (Box 39, Folder 69)
- President of Cornell University, 1862-1949 (Box 39, Folder 70)
- President of Cornell University, 1951-1970 (Box 39, Folder 71)
- Printing Division, 1958-1969 (Box 39, Folder 72)
- University Publications, 1970-1976 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Purchasing Department - Bulletins and Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1951-1970 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Office of the Registrar, 1954-1964 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Office of the Registrar, 1965-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Cornell United Religious Work, 1955-1967 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Research Foundation - Rogers, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- University Conference Coordinator - Rideout, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Traffic Bureau, 1932-1977 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Office of Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1960-1976 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- University Senate, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Statler Club, 1960-1973 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Student Employment, 1970-1976 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Student Policy, 1970-1975 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Treasurer's Ofice, 1948-1976 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Cornell University Trustees, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- University Health Services, 1972-1974 (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Planning and Facilities - Vice President Matyas, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Veterinary College, 1962-1976 (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Personnel Director - Diedrich Willers, 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Correspondence A-Ag, 1956-1971 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Correspondence Ah-Al, 1952-1975 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Correspondence - Am-Aq, 1947-1974 (Box 40, Folder 24)
- American Council on Education, 1951-1973 (Box 40, Folder 25)
- Correspondence Ar-At, 1951-1971 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Correspondence Au-Ay, 1951-1973 (Box 40, Folder 27)
- Correspondence Baa-Bai, 1944-1970 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- Correspondence Bak-Bal, 1950-1972 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Correspondence Bam-Baq, 1943-1959 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Correspondence - Bar, 1949-1975 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- RICOP, University of Delaware - Barwick, Chairman, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Correspondence Bas-Baq, 1949-1952 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- College of Agriculture - Donald Bay, Council Member, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Correspondence Bea-Bec, 1947-1969 (Box 40, Folder 35)
- Correspondence Bed-Bek, 1939-1976 (Box 40, Folder 36)
- Correspondence Bel-Beq, 1951-1974 (Box 40, Folder 37)
- Correspondence Ber-Bey, 1946-1976 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Correspondence Bi, 1945-1975 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Correspondence Bl, 1951-1966 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Correspondence Boa-Bol, 1951-1972 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Correspondence Bom-Bor, 1952-1975 (Box 40, Folder 42)
- Correspondence Bos-Boy, 1947-1967 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Correspondence Bra-Bri, 1944-1973 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- John Brand - University of Connecticut, College of Agriculture, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Correspondence Bro-Bry, 1949-1972 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Correspondence Bua-Buq, 1948-1971 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Correspondence Bur-By, 1945-1962 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Correspondence Ca-Cal, 1957-1971 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Correspondence Cam-Cap, 1950-1973 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Correspondence Car-Cay, 1948-1976 (Box 40, Folder 51)
- Correspondence Ce-Ch, 1945-1979 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Correspondence Ci-Co, 1946-1976 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Correspondence Cog-Col, 1936-1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Com-Cop, 1936-1976 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Cor-Coy, 1942-1974 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Cra-Cry, 1941-1973 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Cu-Cy, 1943-1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Da-Dan, 1940-1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Correspondence Dar-Day, 1952-1974 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Correspondence Dea-Del, 1955-1975 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Dem-Di, 1951-1972 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Doa-Doy, 1938-1972 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Dr-Dy, 1948-1972 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Ea-El, 1946-1976 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Correspondence Em-Ey, 1941-1974 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Fa-Fe, 1968-1974 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Correspondence Fi-Fos, 1962-1975 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Correspondence Fra-Fry, 1953-1973 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Correspondence Ga-Gay, 1963-1976 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Correspondence Ge-Gy, 1953-1972 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Correspondence Ha-Hek, 1960-1976 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Correspondence Hel-Hy, 1942-1974 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Correspondence Ia-In, 1950-1976 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Correspondence Io-Iz, 1945-1969 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Correspondence - Institute of International Education, 1929-1970 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Correspondence Ja-Jy, 1939-1972 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Correspondence Ka-Key, 1951-1976 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Correspondence Ki-Ky, 1944-1975 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Correspondence La-Lew, 1939-1974 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Correspondence Li-Ly, 1938-1973 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Correspondence Ma-Mar, 1940-1975 (Box 41, Folder 31)
- Correspondence Mas-McK, 1939-1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Correspondence McL-Mey, 1938-1972 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Correspondence Mia-Mik, 1944-1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Correspondence Mil-Miz, 1943-1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Correspondence Moa-Moy, 1938-1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Mu-My, 1948-1973 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Na, 1952-1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Correspondence Nea-Nev, 1939-1975 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Correspondence Ne-Ni, 1947-1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Correspondence No-Ny, 1941-1976 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Correspondence Oa-Ok, 1938-1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Ol-Oz, 1950-1974 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Par-Peq, 1952-1974 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Per-Pey, 1940-1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Correspondence - University of Philippines, 1956-1976 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Pl-Py, 1942-1973 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Correspondence Q, 1939-1964 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Correspondence Ra-Rey, 1939-1973 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Correspondence Ria-Rob, 1940-1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Correspondence Roc-Ry, 1939-1975 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Correspondence Sa-Schm, 1948-1975 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Correspondence Scho-Se, 1940-1971 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Correspondence Se, 1938-1950 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Correspondence Se, 1950-1957 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Correspondence Sha-Smy, 1940-1973 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- Correspondence Sn-St, 1945-1975 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Corresponcence Ste-Sy, 1948-1975 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Correspondence SUNY - Empire State College, 1963-1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- CorrespondenceSUNY, 1963-1974 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Correspondence SUNY, 1963-1974 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Correspondence Ta-Th, 1947-1973 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Ti-Ty, 1951-1976 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - Winfield Tyler, 1956-1968 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- UCorrespondence Ua-Uz, 1939-1967 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1953-1973 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - U.S Office of Education, 1964-1974 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Correspondence Va-Vy, 1946-1976 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Waa-Way, 1938-1976 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Wea-Wey, 1948-1973 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Correspondence Wh-Wilk, 1938-1972 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Will-Wy, 1951-1976 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Correspondence Y-Z, 1951-1976 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Teaching Awards, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Accessory Instruction, 1970-1978 (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Director of Administrative Operations, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 20)
- College of Agriculture Admissions, 1970-1976 (Box 43, Folder 21)
- College of Agriculture Advisors, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Agricultural Economics, 1968-1975 (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1967-1976 (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Agronomy, 1969-1975 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Alumni Association, 1968-1974 (Box 43, Folder 26)
- Animal Science, 1966-1976 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1962-1974 (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Business and Finance, 1968-1977 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Basic Educational Opportunity Grant, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Boyce Thompson Institute, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Agriculture Fund, 1972-1976 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Communication Arts, 1967-1975 (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Agricultural Leaders Forum, 1971-1973 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Council for the New York State College of Agriculture, 1969-1974 (Box 43, Folder 35)
- Dean of Agriculture - Palm, 1965-1971 (Box 43, Folder 36)
- Dean of Agriculture - Kennedy, 1966-1976 (Box 43, Folder 37)
- Coordinator of Planning College of Agriculture - Kent, 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 38)
- Associate Dean of Agriculture - Brady, 1971-1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Associate Dean of Agriculture - Spencer, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Biological Science, 1970-1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Biological Science, 1970-1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - Miscellaneous, 1969-1976 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Dean's List, 1972-1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Department Heads, 1966-1972 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Entomology, 1965-1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Environmental Education, 1971-1974 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Extension, 1970-1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Fees - Laboratory, 1973-1977 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1970-1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Food Science, 1967-1975 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Fraternities, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Grants and Contracts, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Home Study Courses, 1970-1973 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Honors Program, 1970-1980 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Intern Program - New York State Assembly, 1972 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Director of International Development - Turk, 1965-1974 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Advisory Committee for International Agriculture, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Mann Library, 1962-1975 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Media Services, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Natural Resources, 1967-1975 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Plant Breeding, 1966-1971 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Plant Pathology, 1965-1979 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Pomology, 1964-1975 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Poultry Science, 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Professor Merit Award, 1947-1976 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Publications for College of Agriculture, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Publications for College of Agriculture, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- Publications for College of Agriculture, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- Publications for College of Agriculture, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- Publications for College of Agriculture, 1979-1980 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Publications for College of Agriculture, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 35)
- Registration, 1971-1972 (Box 44, Folder 36)
- Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 37)
- Research Director, 1968-1972 (Box 44, Folder 38)
- Residency, 1968-1976 (Box 44, Folder 39)
- Rural Development, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 40)
- Rural Sociology, 1970-1971 (Box 44, Folder 41)
- Scholarships and Financial Aid, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 42)
- Staff Achievements, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 43)
- Standing Committees, 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 44)
- Student Council, 1969-1975 (Box 44, Folder 45)
- Student Organizations, 1971-1975 (Box 44, Folder 46)
- Tuition and Fees, 1971-1981 (Box 44, Folder 47)
- Supervisor of Transactions - Tvaroha, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 48)
- Vegetable Crops, 1971-1975 (Box 44, Folder 49)
- Veterans - Students, 1971-1975 (Box 44, Folder 50)
- Employment Study of Graduates from classes of 1949, 1954, 1959, 1964 (Box 45)
- Report on Instruction in Freshman English at Cornell University, 1946-1947 (Box 45)
- Address Cards for Graduates from classes of 1949, 1954, 1959 (Box 46)
- College of Agriculture Budget Ledgers, 1960-1963 (Box 47)
- Employment Study of Graduates from classes of 1949, 1954, 1959 (Box 47)